We're going pick it, pick it for the record with comedian, actress, mom, extraordinaire,
and somebody I just really like, Jasmine W. All right, y'all. Your angry cooking
bits on the internets are hilarious. And I would love to hear for the record,
what is a song that you feel like represents like just anger, like your frustration?
I have a, I have a heartbreak hotel playlist too, because everybody know I'm going through
a divorce, honey. Yeah. How you got a husband and a boyfriend? I don't know.
I was going to let it live. I was going to let it live. I said multitasking. Okay. Anyway,
you know, a heartbreak hotel with Whitney and Faith Evans. Kelly's on that song.
Kelly Price. Yeah. Kelly Price. That song make me mad, but I do love it.
What makes you mad? What are some things that make you mad? I'm mad a lot. I'm an angry black woman.
There's a lot of things that make me mad. I'm upset at like inequality, white supremacy,
injustice. I think people should be treated equally. I think people should be able to live
where they're- What a wild notion.
We should be able to afford to live. Yes, because my parents raised me that way. And my dad,
he always taught me, he said, be the same person every day. Be predictable. Be the type of person
where you come around, people know what to expect. Be reliable. Yeah. Be reliable.
Yeah. I love that. And stand up for people, girl. So yeah, you know, a lot of things make me mad.
We are, we are, we are.